Contact

+972586684457 (Mobile) stevenson2987@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jordan1980 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

SQL

Deep Learning

Machine Learning

Languages

English

Hindi

Telugu

Certifications

IB DP Physics Category 2 Workshop Introduction to Responsible Al Introduction to Generative Al IBDP PHYSICS EXAMINER Introduction to Large Language Models

JORDAN Karangala

Extended essay Coordinator, Head of Physics Dept @ Ebenezer International School Bangalore

Bangalore Urban, Karnataka, India

Summary

As a teacher, I consider my role primarily as a facilitator and as a mentor. As a facilitator I see myself encouraging my wards through classroom experiences and opportunities to take the onus of learning on themselves and creating their own knowledge base thus creating life-long learners. As a mentor, I strive to model leadership, empathy, caring, balance and respect for others. It has been my endeavor, as a teacher to give my students realistic achievable targets and to make their physics learning lively, interesting and practical.

Experience

Ebenezer International School Physics Teacher August 2019 - Present (4 years 11 months) Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Anglican International School Jerusalem
IB Physcis Facilitator
September 2017 - July 2019 (1 year 11 months)
Jerusalem Area, Israel

Lancers International School IBDP PHYSICS TEACHER July 2015 - June 2017 (2 years) Gurgaon, India

DRS International School Physics facilitator 2012 - 2015 (3 years)

IBDP Physics facilitator @ DRS Intl.School handling Physics for IGCSE and IBDP.

Johnson grammar school

IBDP Physics Facilitator June 2010 - May 2012 (2 years)

Planned and executed the activities for students to be taken in an academic session related to the subject as well as co-curricular activities.

Guided students for competitions like Science Olympiad in which they stood first in school and the city.

MERIDIAN SCHOOL

Sr. Sec Physics teacher June 2009 - April 2010 (11 months)

Responsible in maintaining proper unit planners, scheme of work, Internal Assessment records.

As an event organizer, co convened with others, the full responsibilities of organizing pivotal inter school events.

Johnson Grammar School IBDP, ICSE & CBSE Physics Teacher June 2006 - April 2009 (2 years 11 months)

Taught IIT – Foundation physics to grades 8 to 10 Std. State and CBSE Boards.

Examination In-charge: Smooth conduction of the examinations (Internal and External).

House Master: House Master for Agni House. Taking care of house students on daily activities.

Education

Acharya Nagarjuna University

Bachelor's degree, Secondary Education and Teaching \cdot (August 2019 - May 2021)

Physics Department, University college of Sciences, Osmania University

Post Graduate in Physics, Physics (2004 - 2006)

SCC High School

Secondary School Certificate, General Education · (1985 - 1995)